<resources>
    <string name="app_name">RC_Demo</string>
    <string name ="trip_to_tanzania_paragraph_1">Ananya was visiting her friend, Vanessa, in Tanzania. Vanessa
        picked her up from the airport. Vanessa greeted Ananya in Swahili - \'Hujambi  [Hello]\'. Ananya greeted her back
        - \'Habari za asubuhi [Good morning]\'! But that was all Ananya could speak in Swahili. Vanessa could speak in
        English as it is one of the official languages of Tanzania. Vanessa asked her friend, \'Would you like to try
        some local cuisine before heading to the hotel\'? Anaya thought that would be great.
    </string>
    <string name="trip_to_tanzania_paragraph_2"> Ananya started flipping through the menu card. She looked
        confused. There were some interesting names on the Menu card like Ugali, Ndizi Kaanga and Mandazi. She
        did not know what these dishes were, so she asked Venessa, \'Can you please help me out\'? Vanessa started to
        tell Ananya about them. Ugali is a type of Maize porridge. It is served with salad. Ndizi Kanga are
        fried bananas sprinkled with either sugar or salt. Mandazi is fried sweetbread. It is either eaten as a
        snack or a dessert. Venessa also suggested that Ananya should try Tanzanian coffee after lunch. It was
        considered on of the best in the world.\n
        Ananya was still confused. So, Venessa suggested that she could try Mandazi and Ugali. Anaya wanted to know
        more about Tanzania. She asked Venessa, \'Tell me some interesting facts about Tanzania\'.
    </string>
    <string name="trip_to_tanzania_paragraph_3"> Vanessa told Ananya, \'Tanzania is a very diverse country. We have a
        population of 58 million, and there are about 158 tribes in the country. Tanzania was formed in 1964 by uniting
        Tangayika and Zanzibar. The capital of Tanzania is Dodoma\'. \n
        Vanessa explained, \'More than 120 languages are spoken in Tanzania\'! Ananya was amazed by the rich culture and
        diversity if Tanzania. She remarked, \'Tanzania is a diverse country like India\'. Vanessa agreed as she said,
        \'Diversities make our countries colorful\'. \n \n
    </string>
    <string name="the_odorous_knight_paragraph_1">Sir Ducan and his horse were on their way to the king’s palace.
        Sir Ducan was very excited. He sang, \‘I am going to dine with the king, TRALALALALA!
        I like the job of a knight. Yes sir, I do like being a knight.\’
        Sir Ducan smelled sickly as he had not bathed for many days.
        This annoyed his horse. He feared that the other horses at the palace would ridicule him for
        carrying an odorous knight. The horse sighed, \‘I do not like this job, no sir, I don\’t!\’
        Sir Ducan was not happy that his horse was trotting along slowly. He yelled, \‘Faster, boy!
        You just had lunch. Yah!\’ The horse replied furiously, \‘You call that lunch?
        You threw one carrot into my lunch bucket!\’\n
    </string>
    <string name="the_odorous_knight_paragraph_2">Sir Ducan was confused. He asked, 
        \‘Oh! You do not like carrots?\’ The horse corrected Sir Ducan and said, 
        \‘I do like carrots but the nice and juicy ones, not the dry ones that you give me\’. 
        Sir Ducan felt insulted. He scolded the horse,\‘I don’t like the way you are addressing me!\’ 
        The horse could not bear the peculiar odour anymore. He asked, \‘Did you not bathe today? 
        Is that odour coming from you?\’ Sir Ducan replied confidently, \‘Oh! You mean my natural 
        perfume! Do you like it?\’ The horse shockingly retorted, \‘Like?! Do you like it?!\’
    </string>
    <string name="the_odorous_knight_paragraph_3_and_4">Sir Ducan told the horse,
        \‘Of course! One of my ancestors was sprayed by a skunk once. We do like
        the smell. We are proud of it!\’ He then proudly added that the king does
        like the sigil on his shield, which is that of a skunk. The horse snorted
        and said, \‘But he does not like your smell\’.\n
        The horse got an idea to save his grace in front of the other horses.
        He broke into a gallop and suddenly stopped just before a lake.
        Sir Ducan flew off from the back of the horse and fell into the lake.
        Sir Ducan was finally clean. The horse stood beside the lake grinning at
        Sir Ducan who was fuming with anger.
    </string>

</resources>
